Okay, so we've completed this look, the bronze goddess and she looks pretty bronze.
I mean you can tell from her hand to her face that we really, we've really bronzed her up.
So, do you like your look? Yes. Yeah, it looks good on you, your eyes look really blue. This is a good look for anybody really.
If you're brown eyes, blue eyes, green eyes, it doesn't matter, it's a good look for any skin tone, it really doesn't matter.
It's a pretty transitional look for anyone, any hair color even.
So basically you just want to make sure that you bring the stuff with you, you're going to need for touch ups.
Everything is most likely going to stay if you use long wearing makeup, except for your lips and if you tend to get oily in your t-zones, you might want to bring a powder.
Just bring like a little press powder with you, with either a sponge or a travel brush just so you can powder your nose and your forehead and your chin just in case they get a little tiny bit oily.
Because even though this is a doey look, you don't want to look oily or sweaty.
The eyes most like will stay.
The only thing is since we did eyeliner inside the eye, you might want to have to, you might have to reapply that every so often.
So bring your eyeliner with you and that's really easy, you can just throw that in your purse.
And lastly your lip gloss, that the most important.
You want to make sure you bring your lip glosses with you, which ever lip glosses that you mixed if it's one, if it's two, and a little lip brush or you can use your fingertips if you want.
Just make sure your hands are clean.
You want to make sure that you reapply your lip gloss every so often cause that's going to come off pretty much.
Now your blush and your bronzer, it just depends on the person, sometimes it stays.
My blush and bronzer doesn't stay very well on me, so sometimes I like to bring it with me and bring a little travel brush.
You can get little short travel brushes with cases and throw it in your purse just to touch up your blush or your bronzer every so often.
And that's about it, this look is pretty long lasting and it goes, it transitions well from day to evening also.
So that's about it, we're pretty much done with this.